ILGWU. Publications 5780 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Halloween Ball Given by ILGWU: Boston and District Educational Council, 1939 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Convention Festival Concert by the ILGWU Cultural Units, 1940 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- First Annual Grand Ball, 1935 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Annual Grand Ball, 1936 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Hometown, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Fiftieth Anniversary: Cloakmakers Strike of 1910, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Surging Forward: A Pageant of Unionism, 1936 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- What They Wore: Highlights of Fashion History, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 12)
- Campus Wardrobe: A Guide to the Right Clothes for Where You are Going, 1965 (Box 40, Folder 13)
- Your Trousseau and How to Plan It, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 14)
- Looking Your Fashionable Age (Box 40, Folder 15)
- Personne N'Y Croyait (Box 40, Folder 16)
- Coats and Suits and You (Box 40, Folder 17)
- Your Union: A Handbook of Information for Members of the Northeast Department, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 18)
- Proceedings and Resolutions: 3rd Annual Inter-state Conference, 1939 (Box 40, Folder 19)
- How to Be Well-Dressed, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 20)
- Clifford W. Depin de la ILGWU, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Report of Proceedings of the 40th Convention of the ILGWU (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Report of Proceedings of the 41st Convention of the ILGWU, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- ILGWU Souvenir Book, 1941 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Halloween Dance Given by the ILGWU Souvenir Book, 1938 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Halloween Ball Given by ILGWU, 1939 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Report to the 23rd Convention of the ILGWU, 1937 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- The Master Touch (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Garment Worker Merry Christmas! Vol.V, No.1, 1940 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- All There is to Fashion- La Mode Et Ses Secrets (Box 42, Folder 7)
- From the Record (Box 42, Folder 8)
- Garment Worker: Har-Lee Edition (Box 42, Folder 9)
- Underwear Union News- August 1941 (Box 42, Folder 10)
- ILGWU New Courses at the Workers' University, 1928 (Box 42, Folder 11)
- ILGWU 2nd Educational Conference, 1938 (Box 42, Folder 12)
- Announcement of Courses Given in Workers' University, 1924 (Box 42, Folder 13)
- Workers' Education: American and Foreign Experiments, 1921 (Box 42, Folder 14)
- Knowledge is Power: Bulletin 1927-1928, 1917 (Box 42, Folder 15)
- Report of the Educational Activities 1922-1924 (Box 42, Folder 16)
- Announcement 1925-1926 (Box 42, Folder 17)
- Bulletin No.1, 1946 (Box 42, Folder 18)
- Dress Union Presents an Industrial Program (Box 42, Folder 19)
- The Dressmakers' Voice Vol.I, No.2 (Box 42, Folder 20)
- Labor's Record Speaks, 1943 (Box 42, Folder 21)
- Report of Activities: Cotton Dress and Miscellaneous Trades Department (Box 42, Folder 22)
- Statement and Declaration to the Cloakmakers Members of Locals 55, 58, 84, 97, 512 (Box 42, Folder 23)
- Unionism: The Essence of Historic Americanism, 1942 (Box 42, Folder 24)
- Company Unions: A Study Outline with Special Reference to the ILGWU (Box 42, Folder 25)
- The Union Dressmaker Vol.I, No.3, 1934 (Box 42, Folder 26)
- The Word of the Dressmakers (La Parola Del Dressmakers), 1938 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  Italian and English. 2 copies.
- Calling All Shops: Dressmakers' General Strike Bulletin No.1, 1936 (Box 42, Folder 28)
- The Needle Point No.2, 1946 (Box 42, Folder 29)
- The Needle Point No.1 (Box 42, Folder 30)
- The Needle Point (Box 42, Folder 31)
- The Needle Point (Box 42, Folder 32)
- The Needle Point No.3, 1946 (Box 42, Folder 33)
- The Needle Point No.4, 1946 (Box 42, Folder 34)
- The Needle Point No.5, 1936 (Box 42, Folder 35)
- The Needle Point No.6, 1946 (Box 42, Folder 36)
- 33rd ILGWU Convention and Northeast Birthday, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 37)
- Pictorial Chronical Vol. I, No.1, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 38)
- Ladies' Garment Worker Vol.I, No.1, 1932 (Box 42, Folder 39)
- Knitgoods Workers Voice Vol.XIX, No.3, 1956 (Box 42, Folder 40)
- The Knitgoods Worker Strike Preparation Bulletin Vol.I, No.2, 1934 (Box 42, Folder 41)
- Labor and International Relations Labor Lecture Series 14, 1932 (Box 42, Folder 42)
- The Meaning of 1910, 1960 (Box 42, Folder 43)
- Gerektigkeyt (Box 42, Folder 44)
- The Kibitzer June 2, 1934 (Box 42, Folder 45)
- Souvenir Program: Dressmakers' Annual Ball and Floor Show, 1938 (Box 42, Folder 46)
- Convention Souvenir Journal 1902 (Box 42, Folder 47)
- Fourth Annual Convention Souvenir Journal, 1903 (Box 42, Folder 48)
- Sixth International Convention: Annual Journal, 1905 (Box 42, Folder 49)
- Trade Union Relief for Spain. Accounting: Monies Raised and Expended, 1937 (Box 42, Folder 50)
- Dixie- Our No.1 Problem, 1950 (Box 42, Folder 51)
- A Souvenir of the Strike of the Ladies Waist Makers' Union, 1910 (Box 42, Folder 52)
- 4th Annual Dance Journal, 1936 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Ten Years…A Study in Progress, 1943 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Ohio-Kentucky Region Journal: 65th Birthday Nicholas Kirtzman (Box 43, Folder 3)
- The Record 1950-1953: Report to the 28th Convention ILGWU (Box 43, Folder 4)
- New York Cloakmakers on the March!: Highlights of Four Years' Activity (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Greetings to the Delegates of the 25th Convention of the ILGWU (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Trade Union Policies and Tactics Educational Series No.2, 1928 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Guaranteed Yearly Income for Nradis Sportswear Co. Workers (Box 43, Folder 8)
- Tsuey Yohr Yunion-Tetigkeyt (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Berikht Fun Der Juins Board Fun Der Klouk Un Skoyrt Makher Yunion (Box 43, Folder 9)
- David Dubinsky: A Pictorial Biography, 1952 (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Needlepoint, 1948 (Box 43, Folder 11)
- Summary 1948-1949 Series One Day Institutes (Box 43, Folder 12)
- Fiftieth Anniversary Celebration in Honor of Jacob J. Heller, 1940 (Box 43, Folder 13)
- Pacific Coast Federation Official Proceedings and Conferences, 1935-1993 (Box 43, Folder 14)
- Notebook of a Garment Worker-Citizen (Box 43, Folder 15)
- Twentieth Anniversary Reunion of the 1910 Cloakmakers General Strike, 1930 (Box 43, Folder 16)
- Northeast Department Report to the Delegates of the 31st Convention ILGWU, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 17)
- Northeast Department 30th Anniversary 1965 (Box 43, Folder 18)
- A Part of the ILGWU: Report to the Delegates of the 30th ILGWU Convention, 1959 (Box 43, Folder 19)
- Worth Dreaming…, 1959 (Box 43, Folder 20)
- Northeast Report: 1947 to the Delegates of the 26th IGLWU Convention (Box 43, Folder 21)
- Report to the 25th ILGWU Convention, 1944 (Box 43, Folder 22)
- Hometown Union: The Story of the ILGWU in Fall River and Vicinity, 1948 (Box 43, Folder 23)
- Report 1950: ILGWU Golden Jubilee Convention (Box 43, Folder 24)
- East, West, North, South: The Union Hosts are Marching On! (Box 43, Folder 25)
- Ohio-Kentucky Regional ILGWU Conference, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Report of Activities 1945, 1946 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Union Benefits: Medical and Other Benefits in Labor Organizations Bulletin No.3, 1910 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Schedule of Piece Work Prices for Cotton Dresses, Prepared for the Waist and Dressmakers Joint Board, ILGWU, 1938 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Minutes of Department-Wide Conference, 1946 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Staff Training Conference, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- Report of the Educational Department to the Nineteenth Convention of the ILGWU, 1928 (Box 44, Folder 7)
- Garment Jungle Estimating Draft, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 8)
- Ninth Annual Music and Drama Festival, 193 (Box 44, Folder 9)
- Justice ILGWU 60th Anniversary Issue Vol.XLII, No.11-12, 1960 (Box 44, Folder 10)
- ILGWU Magazine, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 11)
- Signature of 450,000, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  This publication is a presentation of the 65th Anniversary Convention of the ILGWU, Miami Beach, FL, May 1965.
- ILGWU News-History 1900-1950 Golden Jubilee Convention (Box 47.1, Folder 1)
- ILGWU Illustrated: 23rd Convention, 1927 (Box 47.1, Folder 2)
- The New York Times: Section 10 Picture of a Union…the ILGWU, 1959 (Box 47.1, Folder 3)
- The Baltimore Jewish Times September 1, 1989 (Box 47.1, Folder 4)
- Scrap Book. The ILG'er, 1959 (Box 47.1, Folder 5)
- Women's Wear Daily: May 23, 1950 Section 2 (Box 47.1, Folder 6)
- Report on the ILGWU Cooperative Village, 1957 (Box 47.1, Folder 7)
- 1944 Convention Report (Box 47.1, Folder 8)
- [No boxes 48 through 56] (Box 48-56)
- Citizen of the Union: The Union- What, Why, How, Where, When (Box 57, Folder 1)
- Everybody Sings, 1942 (Box 57, Folder 2)
- Fire Safety is Fashionable!, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  English and Italian. 4 copies.
- Cards to Members of Congress (Box 57, Folder 4)
- How Many Harvard Lawyers Does it Take to Stop a Union Campaign? (Box 57, Folder 5)
- Labor Sings, 1940 (Box 57, Folder 6)
- The Law Says You Have a Right to Join a Union (Box 57, Folder 7)
  English and French. 2 copies.
- Let's Sing! (Box 57, Folder 8)
- Let's Sing! (Box 57, Folder 9)
- Mooney and Billings Must Be Freed!, 1936 (Box 57, Folder 10)
- The Story of the ILGWU, 1935 (Box 57, Folder 11)
- The Story of the ILGWU, 1951 (Box 57, Folder 12)
- The War is Over! (Box 57, Folder 13)
- What Are Six Things Bosses Always Say When You Try to Form or Join a Union? (Box 57, Folder 14)
- Associate ILGWU Member: AIM for a Better Tomorrow (Box 58, Folder 1)
- Needle News Vol.VI, No.3-13, Vol.VII, No.1-8, 1960-1961 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  19 copies.
- Needle News Vol.VIII, No.1-4, Vol.IX, No.1-6, Vol.X, No.1-4, Vol.XI, No.1-5, Vol.XII, No.2-3, 1963-1967 (Box 58, Folder 3)
- Needle News Vol.XII, No.6-12, Vol.XIII, No.1-7, Vol.XIV, No.1-3, Vol.XV, No.1-2, 1968-1973 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  17 copies.
- Needle News Vol.XXIV, No.3 and Vol.XXVI, No.2, 1982-1998 (Box 58, Folder 5)
- First Annual Grand Ball, 1935 (Box 58, Folder 6)
- Organize! March 1992 (Box 58, Folder 7)
- Garment Worker Vol.I, No.1 and 3, 1956 (Box 58, Folder 8)
- Garment Worker Vol.II, No.1-2, Vol.III, No.2-3, Vol.V, No.1-4, Vol.VI, No.2-8, Vol.VII, No.1 and Vol.VIII, No.1-2, 1957- 1962 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  21 copies.
- Alcohol Abuse Program (Box 58, Folder 10)
- Garment Worker Vol.XXIV, No1, Vol.XXV, No.1-2, Vol.XXVI, No.2, 1981-1983 (Box 58, Folder 10)
- Union Voice Vol.I, Edition 1, 1978 (Box 58, Folder 11)
- Union Voice Vol.1, No.2, 1959 (Box 58, Folder 11)
- Union Voice September-October Issue 1985 (Box 58, Folder 11)
- Union Voice March-April Issue 1986 (Box 58, Folder 11)
- The Needle- February 1957 (Box 58, Folder 12)
- The Needle- Holiday Edition (Box 58, Folder 12)
- The Needle- February 1958 (Box 58, Folder 12)
- Fifty Years of Struggle: The History of the ILGWU in Cincinnati (Box 58, Folder 13)
- Thirty-Fifth Anniversary Jubilee Book, 1945 (Box 58, Folder 14)
- Life in the Cotton Garment and Miscellaneous Trades Department of the ILGWU, 1946 (Box 58, Folder 15)
- Dressmaker's Joint Council Bulletin No.2, 1964 (Box 58, Folder 16)
- Industry Planning Through Collective Bargaining, 1941 (Box 58, Folder 17)
- At Work, At Play (Box 58, Folder 18)
- Eastern States Health and Welfare Fund (Box 58, Folder 19)
- Everybody Sings, 1951 (Box 58, Folder 20)
- Report of the Educational Department, ILGWU: June 1, 1948-May 31, 1950 (Box 58, Folder 21)
- What in the World is the ILGWU Doing? (Box 58, Folder 22)
- Union Sentinel Vol.V, No.1-2, Vol.VI, No.1-2, Vol.VII, No.2, and Vol.VIII, No.2, 1981-1984 (Box 58, Folder 23)
- Safe Stacks: A Worker's Guide to Health and Safety in the Warehouse, 1988 (Box 58, Folder 24)
- Organizing a Health and Safety Committee in the ILGWU (Box 58, Folder 24)
- Safe Stacks: A Worker's Guide to Health and Safety in the Warehouse, 1988 (Box 58, Folder 25)
- Workers' Compensation: Making the System Work for You (Box 58, Folder 26)
- A Union Leader's Guide to Key OSHA Standards, 2001 (Box 58, Folder 27)
- Fire Safety is Fashionable! Materials (Box 58, Folder 28)
- Fire Safety is Fashionable! Rally (Box 58, Folder 29)
- Make Your Workplace Fire Safe, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 30)
- How Many More Must Die?, 1992 (Box 58, Folder 31)
- Miscellaneous Notes (Box 58, Folder 32)
- Looking Out for Your Health: Carpal Tunnel Syndrome and Pennsylvania Workers' Compensation (Box 58, Folder 33)
- Heat (Box 58, Folder 34)
- Formaldehyde (Box 58, Folder 35)
- Cumulative Trauma Disorders (Box 58, Folder 36)
- Do You Know What the VDT in Your Office is Doing to You? (Box 58, Folder 37)
- Medal for a Union: Fifty Years of the ILGWU Union Health Center, 1964 (Box 58, Folder 38)
- Gerechtigkeit: Special Jubilee Issue 1910-1960 (Box 58, Folder 39)
- Midwest Region Union News Vol.I, No.1 and 2, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 40)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board Newsletter, 1963 (Box 58, Folder 41)
- New Englander January 1979 (Box 58, Folder 42)
- New Englander Vol.VI, No.1, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 42)
- New Englander Vol.VII, No.1, 1986 (Box 58, Folder 42)
- New Jersey Region News Vol.I, No.2, 1988 (Box 58, Folder 43)
- New Jersey Region News Vol.I, No.3, 1988 (Box 58, Folder 43)
- 37 Years Young! 1910-1947 (Box 58, Folder 44)
- 75,000 Strong, 1933 (Box 58, Folder 45)
- New York State District News and Views Vol.I, No.2, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 46)
- New York State District News and Views Special Issue Oct.-Nov. 1981 (Box 58, Folder 46)
- New York State District News and Views Spring 1989 (Box 58, Folder 46)
- Double Texture: A Profile of David Gingold, 1953 (Box 58, Folder 47)
- Northeast News: March, 1972 (Box 58, Folder 47)
- ILGWU Health and Welfare Fund, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 48)
- Your Union: A Handbook of Information for Members of the Northeast Department, 1972 (Box 58, Folder 48)
- ILGWU Health and Welfare Fund (Box 58, Folder 48)
- 35 Northeast, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 48)
- 35 Northeast, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 49)
- 35 Northeast, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 50)
- Union Worker Jan.-Feb. 1981 (Box 58, Folder 51)
- A Policy Guide on Enforcing the Union Agreement (Box 58, Folder 52)
- Working Union: You and the ILGWU (Box 58, Folder 52)
- Local 351 Union Worker Vol.VIII, No.1, 1981 (Box 58, Folder 52)
- Union Worker Vol.II, No.1, 1988 (Box 58, Folder 52)
- Northeast News Vol.II, No.1 (Box 58, Folder 52)
- Union Worker- September, 1981 (Box 58, Folder 52)
- ILGWU History and Coloring Book (Box 58, Folder 53)
- Committee of 2… (Box 58, Folder 53)
- A Policy Guide on Enforcing the Union Agreement (Box 58, Folder 53)
- Northeast, Western Pennsylvania and Ohio Department Offensive Against Imports, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 53)
- How to Chair a Meeting (Box 58, Folder 53)
- Task Force on the Survey: Report and Recommendations, 1981 (Box 58, Folder 53)
- A Guide for Taking Par in Local and Shop Meetings (Box 58, Folder 53)
- Some Facts for Stewards (Box 58, Folder 53)
- Ohio State Legislative Report (Box 58, Folder 53)
- Pennsylvania State Legislative Report: Unity House Seminar, 1986 (Box 58, Folder 53)
- Why Do You Pay Dues? (Box 58, Folder 53)
- Why Did You Become a Chairperson? (Box 58, Folder 53)
- The Ohio Sew Biz Vol.III, No.1, 1980 (Box 58, Folder 54)
- The Ohio Sew Biz Vol.4, No.1, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 1)
- The Ohio Sew Biz Vol.5, No.1, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 1)
- The Ohio Sew Biz Vol.VI, No.2, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 1)
- The Ohio Sew Biz Vol.VII, No.2, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 1)
- The Ohio Sew Biz Vol.VIII, No.2, 1984 (Box 59, Folder 1)
- The Voice of Garment Workers (Box 59, Folder 2)
- The Law Says You Have a Right to Join a Union (Box 59, Folder 3)
  English and Spanish. 2 copies.
- How Many Harvard Lawyers Does it Take to Stop a Union Campaign? (Box 59, Folder 3)
- Cuales son las seis cosas que dien los patrones cuando Ud.trata de formar or unirse a la Union? (Box 59, Folder 3)
- Pennsylvania Organizer No.13, 1956 (Box 59, Folder 4)
- Pennsylvania Organizer No.14, 1957 (Box 59, Folder 4)
- Union News (Box 59, Folder 4)
- The PACEsetter Newsletter Vol.I, No.3, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 5)
- Official Proceedings of the Ninth Conference: Pacific Coast Federation, ILGWU, 1942 (Box 59, Folder 6)
- Pacific Northwest District Council News, Issue No.1, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  Spanish and English. 2 copies.
- Pacific Northwest District Council News Issue No.3, 1990 (Box 59, Folder 7)
- Organizers' Dispatch Vol.I, No.1, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 8)
- Organizers' Dispatch Vol.I, No.3, 1980 (Box 59, Folder 8)
- Union News Vol.V, No.2, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 9)
- Union News Vol.IX, No.4, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 9)
- Union News Vol.X, No.1, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 9)
- Union News Vol.X, No.2, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 9)
- Union News Vol.X, No.4, 1988 (Box 59, Folder 9)
- Union News Vol.XI, No.2, 1988 (Box 59, Folder 9)
- Union News Vol.XI, No.3, 1988 (Box 59, Folder 9)
- Union News Vol.XII, No.1, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 9)
- Union News Vol.XII, No.2, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 9)
- Union News Vol.XII, No.3, 1990 (Box 59, Folder 9)
- Union News Vol.XIV, No.3, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 9)
- Union News Vol.XV, No.2, 1992 (Box 59, Folder 9)
- Legislative Newsletter 2/18/69, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 10)
- Legislative Newsletter 4/11/69 (Box 59, Folder 10)
- Legislative Newsletter 2/3/70, 1970 (Box 59, Folder 10)
- Legislative Newsletter 9/1/70, 1970 (Box 59, Folder 10)
- Legislative Newsletter 10/26/72, 1972 (Box 59, Folder 10)
- Legislative Newsletter 10/15/73 (Box 59, Folder 10)
- Legislative Newsletter 6/1/72, 1972 (Box 59, Folder 16)
- Legislative Newsletter 4/1/71, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 16)
- Legislative Newsletter 4/24/74, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 16)
- Legislative Newsletter 4/9/75, 1975 (Box 59, Folder 16)
- Legislative Newsletter 8/7/75, 1975 (Box 59, Folder 16)
- Legislative Newsletter 12/19/75 (Box 59, Folder 16)
- Legislative Newsletter 2/21/78, 1978 (Box 59, Folder 16)
- Legislative Newsletter 6/5/79, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 16)
- Legislative Newsletter 9/21/66 (Box 59, Folder 16)
- Legislative Newsletter 8/23/72, 1972 (Box 59, Folder 16)
- Politics in the '80s: Redrawing the Battlelines, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 17)
- ILGWU Letter 5/14/53, 1953 (Box 59, Folder 17)
- ILGWU Letter 6/19/53 (Box 59, Folder 17)
- ILGWU Letter (Box 59, Folder 17)
- ILGWU Newsletter (Box 59, Folder 17)
- ILGWU Letter 3/17/71, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 17)
- Legislative Newsletter 11/18/1969 (Box 59, Folder 17)
- Memo from the Political Department, 1970 (Box 59, Folder 17)
- Memo from the Political Department (Box 59, Folder 17)
- Location of ILGWU Locals b State and Congressional Districts, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 17)
- Statement on Proposed Changes in the Presidential Election Process, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 17)
- Political Newsletter Vol.I, No.1, 1948 (Box 59, Folder 17)
- Political Newsletter Vol.I, No.2, 1948 (Box 59, Folder 17)
- Statement to the Committee on the Judiciary of the United States House of Representatives (Box 59, Folder 17)
- The 1973 Elections (Box 59, Folder 17)
- An Analysis of Eisenhower's Program (Box 59, Folder 17)
- Your Congressional Scorecard, 1949 (Box 59, Folder 17)
- The Progressive March 1953 (Box 59, Folder 17)
- The Man Who May Be President: Stevenson Speaks (Box 59, Folder 17)
- National Health Insurance Pamphlet (Box 59, Folder 18)
- Bat Boy for Reaction (Box 59, Folder 18)
- Political Bulletin #1 April 1, 1949 (Box 59, Folder 18)
- Political Bulletin #2 April 15, 1949 (Box 59, Folder 18)
- Political Bulletin #3 April 20, 1949 (Box 59, Folder 18)
- Political Bulletin #4 May 25, 1949 (Box 59, Folder 18)
- Political Bulletin #5 June 15, 1949 (Box 59, Folder 18)
- Political Bulletin #6 January 10, 1950 (Box 59, Folder 18)
- Political Bulletin #7 January 27, 1950 (Box 59, Folder 18)
- Political Bulletin #8 March 1, 1950 (Box 59, Folder 18)
- Political Bulletin #10 June 29, 1950 (Box 59, Folder 18)
- What is a Political Steward? (Box 59, Folder 18)
- Report from Washington: GEB Report (Box 59, Folder 18)
- Report from Washington (Box 59, Folder 18)
- PEP Report: 11/17/53 (Box 59, Folder 18)
- PEP Report: 3/16/54 (Box 59, Folder 18)
- PEP Report: 3/18/54 (Box 59, Folder 18)
- PEP Report: 4/27/54 (Box 59, Folder 18)
- PEP Report: 5/28/54 (Box 59, Folder 18)
- PEP Report: 3/23/55 (Box 59, Folder 18)
- PEP Report: 11/22/55 (Box 59, Folder 18)
- Are You Stressed Out? (Box 59, Folder 19)
- The Torch Vol.XIV, No.1, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 20)
- The Torch Vol.XV, No.2, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 20)
- The Torch Vol.XVI, No.1, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 20)
- The Torch Vol.XVII, No.2, 1984 (Box 59, Folder 20)
- Testimony on the Need for Home Health Care, 1976 (Box 59, Folder 21)
- Retirees Guide to Organizing (Box 59, Folder 22)
- Retire Service Department Pamphlet (Box 59, Folder 23)
- Scranton District Bulletin No.7, 1952 (Box 59, Folder 24)
- Scranton District Bulletin No.8, 1952 (Box 59, Folder 24)
- Scranton District Bulletin: May 1958 (Box 59, Folder 24)
- Scranton District Bulletin: June 1958 (Box 59, Folder 24)
- Scranton District Bulletin: December 1, 1958 (Box 59, Folder 24)
- Scranton District Bulletin: January 1959 (Box 59, Folder 24)
- Scranton District Bulletin: February 1959 (Box 59, Folder 24)
- Scranton District Bulletin: March 1959 (Box 59, Folder 24)
- Scranton District Bulletin: May 1959 (Box 59, Folder 24)
- This is a Union Shop. You and the ILGWU (Box 59, Folder 25)
- Unemployed? A Primer on Unemployment Benefits (Box 59, Folder 25)
- Unity Newsletter Vol.X, No.2, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 25)
- District Info Sheet: Volunteer Organizing Committee (Box 59, Folder 25)
- Educational and Enforcement Publications (Box 59, Folder 25)
- 1983-1984 Activities (Box 59, Folder 25)
- "We Care" ILGWU (Box 59, Folder 25)
- The Garment Worker Newsletter, 1937 (Box 59, Folder 26)
- Pictorial Chronicle No.3, 1966 (Box 59, Folder 27)
- The Chronicle Vol.VII, No.1, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 27)
- The Chronicle Vol.VIII, No.1, 1970 (Box 59, Folder 27)
- ILG'er (Box 59, Folder 27)
- On the Move News No.7, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 28)
  Spanish and English.
- Souvenir Journal Golden Jubilee, 1961 (Box 59, Folder 29)
- Outline on the Jobber-Contractor System, 1938 (Box 59, Folder 30)
- Your Union's Member Assistance Program (Box 59, Folder 31)
- The ILGWU Union Health Center (Box 59, Folder 31)
- Pauline Newman (1893-1986) (Box 59, Folder 31)
- ILGWU Union Health Center: Celebrating 74 Years of Service, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 31)
- The ILGWU Union Health Center (Box 59, Folder 32)
- Your Money's Worth, 1978 (Box 59, Folder 33)
- Schedule of Piece Work Prices for the Cotton Dresses, 1938 (Box 59, Folder 34)
- Slant Vol.II, No.2 (Box 59, Folder 35)
- Slant Vol.III, No.4 (Box 59, Folder 35)
- Solidarity Vol.VIII, No.1, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 35)
- Solidarity Vol.IX, No.2, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 35)
- 50th Anniversary Cloak and Suit Operators Union, 1936 (Box 60, Folder 1)
- Banquet in Celebration of Fiftieth Anniversary of Cloak and Suit Operators' Union, Local 1, 1936 (Box 60, Folder 2)
- Local 1-35 in Action Vol.I, No.1, 1978 (Box 60, Folder 3)
- Souvenir Journal to Establish Old Age Fund, 1928 (Box 60, Folder 4)
- Second Souvenir Journal Old Age and Relief Funds, 1936 (Box 60, Folder 5)
- Amalgamated Ladies Garment Cutters' Union Fiftieth Anniversary, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 6)
- 1902-1962 Almanac (Box 60, Folder 7)
- Resolution Marking the 90th Anniversary of Local 10, 1992 (Box 60, Folder 8)
- Benjamin Hooks, 1992 (Box 60, Folder 8)
- Third Anniversary Historical Edition, 1918 (Box 60, Folder 9)
- Third Anniversary Historical Edition, 1918 (Box 60, Folder 10)
- Journal, 1935 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  English and Yiddish.
- 50 Golden Years Waterproof Garment Workers' Union, 1960 (Box 60, Folder 12)
- Local 20 Record Vol.I, No.2, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 13)
- Local 20 Record Vol.I, No.3, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 13)
- Local 20 Record Vol.I, No.4, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 13)
- Local 20 Record Vol.I, No.5, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 13)
- Local 20 Record Vol.I, No.6, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 13)
- Local 20 Record Vol.II, No.1, 1972 (Box 60, Folder 13)
- Local 20 Record Vol.II, No.3, 1972 (Box 60, Folder 13)
- Local 20 Record Vol.II, No.4, 1972 (Box 60, Folder 13)
- Local 20 Record Vol.II, No.5, 1972 (Box 60, Folder 13)
- Local 20 Record Vol.II, No.6, 1972 (Box 60, Folder 13)
- Local 20 Record Vol.III, No.1, 1973 (Box 60, Folder 13)
- Local 20 Record Vol.III, No.2, 1973 (Box 60, Folder 13)